{
  "questions": [
    {
      "number": 1,
      "question": "Meaning of prominent",
      "answers": [ "difficult seen", "easily seen", "easily said" ], "correct_answer": 2
    },
    {
      "number": 2,
      "question": "Meaning of ablaze",
      "answers": [ "burning strongly", "burning loosly", "burning easily" ], "correct_answer": 1
    },
    {
      "number": 3,
      "question": "Meaning of chaos",
      "answers": [ "easily seen ", "complete burning", "complete confusion" ], "correct_answer": 3
    },
    {
      "number": 4,
      "question": "The line at which sky meets ground",
      "answers": [ "tripad", "horizon", "ablaze" ], "correct_answer": 2
    },
    {
      "number": 5,
      "question": "A three legged structure",
      "answers": [ "tripad", "horizon", "ablaze" ], "correct_answer": 1
    },
    {
      "number": 6,
      "question": "Looked with difficulty because of the smoke",
      "answers": [ "choas", "ablaze", "peered" ], "correct_answer": 3
    },
    {
      "number": 7,
      "question": "(Write) Why was narrator returning to may bury",
      "answers": [ "to see how the war would end", "between Martions and humans",
                   "He was confident that humans will easily win", "all" ], "correct_answer": 4
    },
    {
      "number": 8,
      "question": "(Write) Describe the thing that the narrator saw",
      "answers": [ "He saw a tripod higher that house", "It looked like walkoing machine", "both" ], "correct_answer": 3    },
    {
      "number": 9,
      "question": "(Write) What was the narrator thinking about",
      "answers": [ "He was thinking about", "red glow on the horizon", "and black cloud in sky", "all" ], "correct_answer": 4
    },
    {
      "number": 10,
      "question": "(Write) Hod did the narrator's neighbour look",
      "answers": [ "All shops and houses were burned", "There was smoke everywere", "There were no people around", "all" ], "correct_answer": 4
    },
    {
      "number": 11,
      "question": "(Write) What were the three tripods doing when the two men saw them in the morning",
      "answers": [ "They were standing on the playground", "and surveying the damage they had done", "both" ], "correct_answer": 3
    },
    {
      "number": 12,
      "question": "(Write) Why did the narrator fall into the pool",
      "answers": [ "He pulled his horse's head in panic", "His cart toppled and he fall into the pool",
                   "both" ], "correct_answer": 3
    },
    {
      "number": 13,
      "question": "(Write) What did the narrator do to reach his house",
      "answers": [ "He ran through the woods in the darkness", "Walked", "Laughed" ], "correct_answer": 1
    },
    {
      "number": 14,
      "question": "(Write) What did the narrator fall down over",
      "answers": [ "He fell down over remains of neighbourhood shop", "Martians had burned it down", "both" ], "correct_answer": 3
    },
    {
      "number": 15,
      "question": "(Write) What did he understand when he realized what it was",
      "answers": [ "He realized that the Martians had attacked his neighbourhood", "And Martians had defeated the army", "both" ], "correct_answer": 3
    },
    {
      "number": 16,
      "question": "(Write) HOw did the speaker wonder about this",
      "answers": [ "He wondered weather martians were just machines", "which could think and take decisions", "both" ], "correct_answer": 3
    },
    {
      "number": 17,
      "question": "(Write) Was he able to find out what martians really are",
      "answers": [ "No", "zzz", "He did not find whather the martians were intelligent machines or not", "both" ], "correct_answer": 3
    }
  ]
}

